Finding Aid for the Kelly Miller Smith Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- WRITINGS
  - The Sermon on the Mount (Life in the Kingdom of God), The Revolutionary Teaching, Outline for the Baptist Bible Conference, undated (Box 114, Folder 14)
  - Sermons of the Black Pastor, undated (Box 114, Folder 15)
  - Structure for Crisis Proclamation, undated (Box 114, Folder 16)
  - The Struggle for Equality Then and Now, undated (Box 114, Folder 17)
  - The Stuff We Use, undated (Box 114, Folder 18)
  - Thanks for Our Bible, undated (Box 114, Folder 19)
  - They Who Preach, 1980 (Box 114, Folder 20)
  - They Kingdom Come, undated (Box 114, Folder 21)
  - Time is Winding Up!, undated (Box 114, Folder 22)
  - The Translucent Darkness, Lecture, undated (Box 114, Folder 23)
  - Through a Glass Blackly, undated (Box 114, Folder 24)
  - Trip to the Democratic Republic of the Congo Observations and Suggestions, undated (Box 114, Folder 25)
  - Untitled, Lecture, 1968 (Box 114, Folder 26)
  - Viewing the 70s Through a Dark Window, undated (Box 114, Folder 27)
  - The Western Missionary Enterprise and the Third World: Problems and Challenges, undated (Box 114, Folder 28)
  - What Social Crisis?, undated (Box 114, Folder 29)
  - Whitfield, undated (Box 114, Folder 30)
  - Wilderness 101, 1981 (Box 114, Folder 31)
  - Worship in the Black Church, 1975 (Box 114, Folder 32)
  - The Young Adult, edited by Kelly Miller Smith, 1958 - 1959 (Box 114, Folder 33)
  - Book Review — Comments on Paris' Black Leaders in Conflict, undated (Box 114, Folder 34)
- MINISTERIAL CAREER
  - First Baptist Church, Capitol Hill (Box 114)
  - The Beacon, December 8, 1979 - May 11, 1980 (Box 114, Folder 35)
  - Building Program (Box 114, Folder 36)
  - Calendars, 1968 - 1981 (Box 114, Folder 37)
  - Directory, 1971 (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Financial information (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Kelly Miler Smith Towers (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Mailing Lists (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - Membership Handbook, 1962 - 1969 (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - Membership Handbook, 1970 - 1973 (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - Membership Handbook, 1974 - 1975 (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - Membership Handbook, 1976 - 1982 (Box 115, Folder 8)
  - Memoranda (2) February 29, 1972 - April 10, 1978 (Box 115, Folder 9)
  - Minutes, June 9, 1964 - May 17, 1978 (Box 115, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1967 - 1983, undated (Box 115, Folder 11)
  - Outreach, 1978 (Box 115, Folder 12)
  - Press Releases, undated (Box 115, Folder 13)
  - Program Proposals, 1978, undated (Box 115, Folder 14)
  - Special Events, An Evening of Music, 1981 (Box 115, Folder 15)
  - Special Events, Annual Youth Day, 1983 (Box 115, Folder 16)
  - Special Events, Annual Youth Oratorical Contest, 1980 (Box 115, Folder 17)
  - Special Events, Appreciation Banquet Honoring the Rev. Kelly Miller Smith, 1961 (Box 115, Folder 18)
  - Special Events, Celebration of the Life of Mrs. Esther Beatrice Jackson Ewing, 1983 (Box 115, Folder 19)
  - Special Events, Special Events, Centennial Celebration, 1965 (Box 115, Folder 20)
  - Special Events, Children's Summer Recreational, Educational and Religious Activity Program, undated (Box 115, Folder 21)
  - Special Events, Christian Education in Black Churches Seminar, 1977 (Box 115, Folder 22)
  - Special Events, Dedication, 1972 (Box 115, Folder 23)
  - Special Events, Easter Meditation, undated (Box 115, Folder 24)
  - Special Events, Funeral Services of Charles Bradford Steele, Sr. 1983 (Box 115, Folder 25)
  - Special Events, Groundbreaking Ceremonies, 1970 (Box 115, Folder 26)
  - Special Events, Honoring the Rev. Kelly Miller Smith, Sr., 1976 (Box 115, Folder 27)
  - Special Events, In Worship With Tennessee State Prison, 1976 (Box 115, Folder 28)
  - Special Events, The Kennedy Family, 1981 (Box 115, Folder 29)
  - Special Events, Love Transcending, undated (Box 115, Folder 30)
  - Special Events, Loyalty Day, 1974 (Box 115, Folder 31)
  - Special Events, Loyalty Dinner, 1975 (Box 115, Folder 32)
  - Special Events, National Youth Week, 1961 (Box 115, Folder 33)
  - Special Events, Ninety-Fourth Anniversary Celebration, 1959 (Box 115, Folder 34)
  - Special Events, Obsequies of Mrs. Linella Elizabeth Long Pope, 1983 (Box 115, Folder 35)
  - Special Events, On the Occasion of the 25th Anniversary of Rev. Kelly Miller Smith, 1976 (Box 115, Folder 36)
  - Special Events, Revivals, 1973 - 1978 (Box 115, Folder 37)
  - Special Events, Spring Lecture Series, 1983 (Box 115, Folder 38)
  - Special Events, Tennessee Baptist Leadership Education Congress, 1973 (Box 115, Folder 39)
  - Special Events, Thirty Years in Retrospect, 1981 (Box 115, Folder 40)
  - Special Events, The Thirty-First Year, 1982 (Box 115, Folder 41)
  - Special Events, 20th Anniversary of Rev. Kelly Miller Smith, 1971 (Box 115, Folder 42)
  - Special Events, 28th Anniversary of Rev. Kelly Miller Smith, 1979 (Box 115, Folder 43)
  - Special Events, A Twin Anniversary Celebration, 1952 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Special Events, We Care About People!, 1979 (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - The Torch, 1962 - 1972 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - The Torch, 1973 - 1974 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - The Torch, 1975 (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - The Torch, 1976 (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - The Torch, 1977 (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - The Torch, 1978 (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - The Torch, 1979 (Box 116, Folder 9)
  - The Torch, February, 1980 - June, 1980 (Box 116, Folder 10)
  - The Torch, July, 1980 - December, 1980 (Box 116, Folder 11)
  - The Torch, January, 1981 - June, 1981 (Box 116, Folder 12)
  - The Torch, July, 1981 - December, 1981 (Box 116, Folder 13)
  - The Torch, January 1982 - June 1982 (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - The Torch, August 1982 - December 1982 (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - The Torch, January 1983 - May 1983 (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - The Torch, June 1983 - March 1984 (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - Weekly Programs, 1965 - 1984 Other Churches and Institutions (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - Agricultural, Mechanical and Normal College, 1959 (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - Alemeda Street Christian Church, 1983 (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - Antioch Baptist Church, 1960 - 1963 (Box 117, Folder 8)
  - Bethany Baptist Church, 1975 (Box 117, Folder 9)
  - Bethesda Baptist Church, 1975 (Box 117, Folder 10)
  - Brown Memorial Presbyterian Church, 1975 (Box 117, Folder 11)
  - The Chansonettes, 1948 (Box 117, Folder 12)
  - Colgate Rochester Divinity School, 1975 (Box 117, Folder 13)
  - Church Street Cumberland Presbyterian Church 1983 (Box 117, Folder 14)
  - Euclid Avenue Christian Church, 1982 (Box 117, Folder 15)
  - Farish Street Missionary Baptist Church, 1977 (Box 117, Folder 16)
  - Gay-Lea Christian Church, 1961 (Box 117, Folder 17)
  - Grambling College, undated (Box 117, Folder 18)
  - Jackson College, 1954 (Box 117, Folder 19)
  - Liberty Baptist Church, 1975 - undated (Box 117, Folder 20)
  - Little Zion Primitive Baptist Church, 1981 (Box 117, Folder 21)
  - Mount Heroden Church, 1948 - 1978, undated (Box 117, Folder 22)
  - Mt. Zion Baptist Church, Nashville, 1981 (Box 117, Folder 23)
  - Mt. Zion Baptist Church, Seattle, 1960 - 1975 (Box 117, Folder 24)
  - National Chaplains Association for Youth Rehabilitation, 1974 (Box 117, Folder 25)
  - Naval Amphibious Base Chapel, 1980 (Box 117, Folder 26)
  - Oklahoma State Baptist Ministers' Institute, 1955 (Box 117, Folder 27)
  - Olivet Institutional Baptist Church, 1978 (Box 117, Folder 28)
  - Omega Psi Phi Fraternity, 1957 (Box 117, Folder 29)
  - Pleasant Green Baptist Church, 1982 (Box 117, Folder 30)
  - Second Baptist Church, Missouri, 1980 (Box 117, Folder 31)
  - Second Baptist Church, New York, 1975 (Box 117, Folder 32)
  - Second Community Church, 1975 (Box 117, Folder 33)
  - Spelman College, 1975 (Box 117, Folder 34)
  - Union, undated (Box 117, Folder 35)
  - Zion Baptist Church, undated (Box 117, Folder 36)
- VANDERBILT DIVINITY SCHOOL
  - Class Materials and Courses
  - Schedules, 1970 - 77, undated (Box 117, Folder 37)
  - The Beginning of Christian Themes in Black American Art (Lilly Seminar), 1979 (Box 117, Folder 38)
  - The Black Church and Black Liberation (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - The Black Church and Contemporary Social Problems (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - The Black Church in America, Class Survey (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - The Black Church in America, Course Bibliography and Reading Material (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - The Black Church in America Schedule of Lectures Student Grades Student Papers (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - The Black Church in America, Student Papers (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - The Black Church in America Student Registration, 1970 - 1982 Syllabi, 1973 - 1982, undated (Box 118, Folder 7)
  - The Black Pastor as Community Strategist (Box 118, Folder 8)
  - The Black Pastor in U.S.A. (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - The Black Religious Experience (Box 118, Folder 10)
  - Black Religious Leadership (Box 118, Folder 11)
  - Book Lists, Bibliographies (Box 118, Folder 11)
  - Financial Information (Box 118, Folder 11)
  - Notes (Box 118, Folder 11)
  - Black Religious Leadership (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - Press Releases Reading Material Student Grades Student Papers (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - Black Religious Leadership (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - Student Registration Syllabi, 1976 - 1983, undated (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - Community Organization and Black Culture (Lilly Seminar), 1979 (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - Foundations of Preaching (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - Lilly Seminar for Black Ministers, 1977 (Box 119, Folder 5)
  - Preaching and Contemporary Problems (Box 119, Folder 6)
  - Preaching and Social Crises (Box 119, Folder 7)
  - Article Reprint (marked) (Box 119, Folder 7)
  - Book Lists, Bibliography (Box 119, Folder 7)
  - Course Evaluations (Box 119, Folder 7)
  - Notes (Box 119, Folder 7)
  - Preaching and Social Crises, Student Papers (Box 119, Folder 8)
  - Preaching and Social Crises, Student Papers (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - Preaching and Social Crises Student Registration, 1973 - 1982 Syllabi, 1973 - 1982, undated (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Reading in Church and Public Life (Box 119, Folder 11)
  - Readings in Parish Problems (Box 119, Folder 12)
  - Readings in Philosophical Theology (Box 119, Folder 13)
  - Religion and Education in the Black Experience (Lilly Seminar), 1978 (Box 119, Folder 14)
  - Religion and Health Care Services in the Black Experience (Lilly Seminar), 1978 (Box 119, Folder 15)
  - Religion and Society in the Black Experience (Lilly Seminar), 1977 - 1979 (Box 119, Folder 16)
  - Book Lists, Bibliography (Box 119, Folder 16)
  - Course Evaluation (Box 119, Folder 16)
  - Religion and Society in the Black Experience (Lilly Seminar), 1977 - 1979 (Box 119, Folder 17)
    - Lectures:
    - Mansfield Douglas, III, "Religious and Society in the Black Experience"
    - Lloyd C. Elam, M.D., "The Black Church and Health"
    - Walter E. Fauntroy, "The Social Action Mission of the Black
    - Church" (marked) Walter Searcy, "Religion and Society in the Black Experience"
    - Jesse H. Turner, "Economic Issues of the Black Church"
  - Religion and Society in the Black Experience (Lilly Seminar), 1977 - 1979 (Box 119, Folder 18)
  - Memoranda (10), November 14, 1977 - July 16, 1979 (Box 119, Folder 18)
  - Newspaper Clipping, December 2, 1977 (Box 119, Folder 18)
  - Press Release, September 16, 1977 - March 26, 1979, undated (Box 119, Folder 18)
  - Student Grades (Box 119, Folder 18)
  - Religion and Society in the Black Experience, Student Papers (Box 119, Folder 19)
  - Religion and Society in the Black Experience (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Student Registration Syllabi, 1977 - 1979 (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Religious Thought of Howard Thurman (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - Article Reprints Book Lists and Bibliographies Brochure (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - Certificate of Participation (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - Religious Thought of Howard Thurman (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - List of Tapes by Thurman (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - The Listening Ear, newsletter, Fall, 1980 (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - Press Releases, December 13 - 17, 1974 (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - Student Grades Student Papers (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - Religious Thought of Howard Thurman, Student Papers (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Religious Thought of Howard Thurman Student Registration, 1975 - 1983 Syllabi, 1975 - 1983, undated Thurman Vitae (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - Theology and the Black Experience (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - Dissertation Proposals (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - Field Education Program: Guidelines (Box 120, Folder 8)
  - Student Contacts; Student Evaluation (Box 120, Folder 9)
  - Student Placement Lists, 1970 - 1982 (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Lilly Seminar Applications, Anderson - King (Box 120, Folder 11)
  - Lilly Seminar Applications, Kirk - Wynn (Box 120, Folder 12)
  - Lilly Seminar Participants (Box 120, Folder 13)
  - Lilly Seminar Travel Reports (Box 120, Folder 14)
  - Student Papers, Kelly Miller Smith, Jr. (Box 120, Folder 15)
  - Student Papers, Corry - Lewis (Box 120, Folder 16)
  - Student Papers, Ragland - Woodyard, no name (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - Unidentified Course Material Conferences and Other Events (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Agenda for the Contemporary Church, April 1971 (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - The Bible and the Black Experience, February 1978 (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - The Black Church and Black Economic Development in Nashville, March 1973 (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - The Black Church: Response to Racism, April 1970 (Box 121, Folder 6)
  - The Black Messiah, November 1970 (Box 121, Folder 7)
  - The Black Pastor as Counselor, February 1977 (Box 121, Folder 8)
  - The Burden of Black Religion, undated (Box 121, Folder 9)
  - Christian Education in Black Churches, October 1977 (Box 121, Folder 10)
    - "Christian Education in Black Churches," speech by Grant Shockley Discovering the Content of Curriculum Resources
    - Financial Information
    - Memoranda (6), September 27 - November 8, 1977
  - Christian Education in Black Churches, October 1977 (Box 121, Folder 11)
    - Planning Committee Membership List
    - Planning Committee Minutes, August 2 - September 16, 1977
    - Press Release
    - Programs
    - Registration Lists
  - The Church and Social Issues (Box 121, Folder 12)
  - The Church in Africa (Cole Lectures), February 1979 (Box 121, Folder 13)
  - Clowns, Clerics and Clergy Women: Reflections on the Church, undated (Box 121, Folder 14)
  - Community Leaders Conferences, April 1973 - May 1978 (Box 121, Folder 15)
  - Conference on the Black Family and the Black Church, November 1972 (Box 121, Folder 16)
  - Conference on the Church and the Black Elderly, November 1974 (Box 121, Folder 17)
  - Conference on the Church and Social Responsibility, undated (Box 121, Folder 18)
  - Commentary 1981 (Faith and Politics: The Challenge of the New Religious Right), November 1981 (Box 121, Folder 19)
  - Consolation on the Black Church, undated (Box 121, Folder 20)
  - Contemporary Social Problems and the Function on the Church, April, 1982 (Box 121, Folder 21)
  - The Dawson Five, April, undated (Box 121, Folder 22)
  - Death in the Black Experience (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - Eschatology and Activism in the Black Tradition, January 1982 (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - The Future Context of Christian Belief (Cole Lecture), April 1970 (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - Hans King Lectures Trip, November 1980 (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - Literature and Resources for the Black Church, December 1979 (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - The Marketing of Religion, undated (Box 122, Folder 6)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr., Memorial Observance, January 1973 (Box 122, Folder 7)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr., Memorial Dinner and Consultation, April 1975 (Box 122, Folder 8)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr., Memorial Observance, April 1979 (Box 122, Folder 9)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr., Second Annual Lecture, January 1983 (Box 122, Folder 10)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr., Memorial Observance, April 1983 (Box 122, Folder 11)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. as Social Crisis Preacher, September 1973 (Box 122, Folder 12)
  - The Mythic Structure of Racism, undated (Box 122, Folder 13)
  - Nat Turner Day and the Myth of the Old South, undated (Box 122, Folder 14)
  - The Parabolic in Religion and Literature (Cole Lectures) February - April 1978 (Box 122, Folder 15)
  - Pastoral Care in Black Perspective, March 1979 (Box 122, Folder 16)
  - Pastoral Counseling from the Perspective of a Black Pastor, February 1977 (Box 122, Folder 17)
  - Philosophical, Poetical, and Religious Speaking, March, undated (Box 122, Folder 18)
  - Racism, Racists and Theological Education, February 1971 (Box 122, Folder 19)
  - Religion in Contemporary America (Cole Lectures) February - April 1977 (Box 122, Folder 20)
  - Religious Faith and Contemporary Social Crises, April 1982 (Box 122, Folder 21)
  - Religious Leadership and the Needs of the Black Community, April 1973 (Box 122, Folder 22)
  - Theological Education Workshop, October 1979 (Box 122, Folder 23)
    - Agenda
    - List of Persons Invited to Participate
    - List of Persons Writing Papers for the Workshop
    - Memoranda (2), September 14, 1979 - January 2, 1980
    - Papers:
      Donald F. Beisswenger, "Approaches to the Integration of Academic and Practical"
      Edward Farley, "A Report on the Theological Education Workshop"
      James F. Hopewell, "Parish as Paradigm"
      Joseph C. Hough, Jr., "Reform in Theological Education as Political Task"
      Lawrence N. Jones, "Response to Edward Farley"
      Lawrence N. Jones, "Response to Robert Lynn"
      Leander Keck, "Remarks Preliminary to Reflections on the Papers"
  - Theological Education Workshop, October 1979 (Box 122, Folder 24)
    - Papers:
    - Robert Wood Lynn, "Notes Toward a History: Theological Encyclopedia and the Evolution of American Seminary Curriculum, 1808 - 1968"
    - William F. May, "Theological Education: Beyond Adam Smith"
    - Thomas W. Ogletree, "The Quest for Theologia and the Reform of Theological Education"
    - George Rupp, "Theological Education as the Historical-Critical Appropriation of Traditions"
    - David Tracy, "A Partial Response to Documents in Theological Education"
    - Barbara G. Wheeler, "Response to Farley's and Lynn's Papers: Some Additional Considerations"
  - Miscellaneous (Folder 24)
  - American Religious Bibliography Seminar (Box 122, Folder 25)
  - Class Schedules, 1969 - 1983 (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - Course Evaluation: The Divinity School (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - Courses of Study, Outline (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - Examination Schedule, 1975 (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - Final Examinations and Study Guides (Box 123, Folder 5)
  - Orientation Schedule, VDS and GDR 1977 (Box 123, Folder 6)
  - Reserve Statistics Reports, 1979 - 1981 (Box 123, Folder 7)
  - Sex Class Participants, undated (Box 123, Folder 8)
  - Syllabi, 1971 - 1983, undated (Box 123, Folder 9)
  - Textbook Lists, 1968 - 1974 (Box 123, Folder 10)
  - Textbook Lists, 1976 - 1982, undated (Box 123, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Communications (Box 123, Folder 11)
  - Academic Policies, 1973 - 1975 (Box 123, Folder 12)
  - Admissions and Enrollment Statistics, 1969 - 1983 (Box 123, Folder 13)
  - Admissions and Scholarship Committee, 1970 (Box 123, Folder 14)
  - Advancement Committee, 1979 - 1980, undated (Box 123, Folder 15)
  - Alumni Newsletter, 1969 - 1974 (Box 123, Folder 16)
  - An Experiment in Transcultural Communication Values, Proposal, undated (Box 123, Folder 17)
  - A Bibliography of Black Methodism, 1970 (Box 123, Folder 18)
  - Black Church Management Seminar (A Proposal), undated (Box 123, Folder 19)
  - Black Studies Committee, 1968 - 1971, undated (Box 123, Folder 20)
  - Black Student Enrollment, 1970 - 1982, undated (Box 123, Folder 21)
  - Board of Advisors, 1980 - 1983, undated (Box 123, Folder 22)
  - Book Reviews (Box 123, Folder 23)
  - Brochures (Box 123, Folder 24)
  - The Church and Moral Education, Proposal, 1974 (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - Committee on Community Life and Public Events (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Special Programs (Box 124, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Student Affairs (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - The Communicator, September 2, 1977 - March 14, 1983 (Box 124, Folder 5)
  - Curriculum and Theological Education Committee (Box 124, Folder 6)
  - Doctor of Ministry Committee and Program (Box 124, Folder 7)
  - Education for Practicing Black Ministers, Proposal, 1972 (Box 124, Folder 8)
  - Elredge, James Foster, January - August 1980 (Box 124, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Assignments (Box 124, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Meeting Agendas and Minutes, September 24. 1968 - December 18, 1969 (Box 124, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Meeting Agendas and Minutes, January 15 - December 11, 1970 (Box 124, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Meeting Agendas and Minutes, January 22 - December 16, 1971 (Box 124, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Meeting Agendas and Minutes, January 28 - December 8, 1972 (Box 124, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Meeting Agendas and Minutes, January 12 - December 7, 1973 (Box 124, Folder 15)
  - Faculty Meeting Agendas and Minutes, January 12 - December 13, 1974 (Box 124, Folder 16)
  - Faculty Meeting Agendas and Minutes, January 17 - December 12, 1975 (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Meeting Agendas and Minutes, January 9 - December 10, 1976 (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Meeting Agendas and Minutes, January 14 - November 11, 1977 (Box 125, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Meeting Agendas and Minutes, January 20 - December 8, 1978 (Box 125, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Meeting Agendas and Minutes, January 12 - December 14, 1979 (Box 125, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Meeting Agendas and Minutes, January 11 - December 12, 1980 (Box 125, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Meeting Agendas and Minutes, January 16 - November 13, 1981 (Box 125, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Meeting Agendas and Minutes, January 22, 1982 - May 13, 1983 (Box 125, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Newsletter, September 11, 1968 - October 16, 1973, undated (Box 125, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Rosters, 1968 - 1978 (Box 125, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Senate (Box 125, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Skit, 1980 (Box 125, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Workshop on Curricular Planning, January 8, 1979 (Box 125, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Writings, Bibliography, 1978 - 1979 (Box 125, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Writings (Box 125, Folder 15)
  - Beisswenger, D.F., "Panel Presentation to Institute in Racism and Theological Education,", undated (Box 125, Folder 15)
  - Buttrick, David, "Controversy-Pronouncement Stories in the Synoptics,", undated (Box 125, Folder 15)
  - Buttrick, David, "Homiletics/Liturgics: A Survey Memo,", undated (Box 125, Folder 15)
  - Crenshaw, James L., 'The Art of Story Telling in the Hebrew Bible,", undated (Box 125, Folder 15)
  - Crenshaw, James L., "Eulogy: Joseph Daniel Bobo,", 1983 (Box 125, Folder 15)
  - Crenshaw, James L., "The International Organization for the Study of the Old Testament,", undated (Box 125, Folder 16)
  - Crenshaw, James L., "Proposal for an Overtures Volume,", undated (Box 125, Folder 16)
  - Crenshaw, James L., "Story and Faith in the Old Testament," manuscript, undated (Box 125, Folder 16)
  - Donahue, John R., "Education for Justice,", undated (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - Farley, Edward, "Can Practical Theology Be Both a Hermeneutics of Praxis and a Theology of the Contemporary Action of the Church and its Leadership?", undated (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - Farley, Edward, "The Problem of Ecclesiastes and the Good News of Jesus Christ,", undated (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - Farley, Edward, "Process Theology,", undated (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - Farley, Edward, "The Reform of Theological Education as a Theological Task,", undated (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - Forstman, Jack, "Charge to the Graduates,", May 15, 1981 (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - Forstman, Jack, "On the Optimal Use of Faculty as a Time of Budgetary Restraints,", undated (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - Harrelson, Walter, "The Trial of Joshua the High Priest — Zechariah 3,", undated (Box 126, Folder 2)
  - Harrod, Howard L., "Comment: Peter Berger's The Heretical Imperative,", undated (Box 126, Folder 2)